# TANYO IVANOV

23 PRETORIA RD, E16 4NP / (44) 07383721742 / TIVANOV@TAKERMAN.NET
TWITTER: @TANYOIVANOV / LINKEDIN: @TANYO-IVANOV / GITHUB: TAKERMAN /
WWW.TANYOIVANOV.NET

#### PERSONAL STATEMENT

I am a Software Developer with 7 years of experience in custom software development. As a developer, I am competent at understanding the project's needs, ensuring high standards of code quality and contributing to a warm and welcoming atmosphere. I am looking for a full-time position.

#### **WORK HISTORY**

Full-Stack .NET Developer – Contract – Remote

February 2020 - July 2020

OneDigital Tech, Outsourcing to SMS Ferries

In my role at OneDigital Tech, I worked on an existing API for the invoicing of cargo ships. My main duty was to change the way of invoicing and to introduce new charges to the system. I also took part in the Angular 8 front-end layer development and sprints planning.

Tech Stack: ASP.NET Core Web API, Angular 8, Angular Material, Entity Framework Core, SQL Server

Application Developer – Permanent – London, UK

January 2019 – December 2019

Foster + Partners, Architecture

Took an important part of the development and testing of the new Intranet and all the accompanying applications(~20). My role also included helpdesk tickets handling, new internal microservice development, everyday communication with the employees. Impeccable knowledge in many technologies was key to this position. I left purely because of family reasons.

Tech Stack: ASP.NET Core MVC/Web API, ASP.NET WebForms/MVC, WinForms, Azure, Vue.js, Umbraco, Selenium, xUnit Tests, SQL Server, EntityFramework Core, Bootstrap, jQuery

Senior .NET Developer – Permanent – Plovdiv, Bulgaria

June 2016 - November 2018

**BGO Software, Outsourcing to the NHS** 

In this role, I was responsible for the software development and maintenance of a public portal (https://harp.org.uk) of the NHS related to health researches. My main daily tasks included bug fixing, new features development, helpdesk tickets handling, client-team communication and planning, junior developers introduction.

Tech Stack: ASP.NET MVC/WebForms, SQL Server, EF, jQuery, Ace Admin, Bootstrap, CI/CD, Jira

.NET Developer - Permanent - Bulgaria and Sweden

June 2015 - June 2016

Comstream, Outsourcing to eGain

Worked in the client location in Gothenburg on an ASP.NET MVC installer application of IoT devices who decreases the buildings overall energy consumption. I was responsible for the application development and mentoring of a junior developer.

Tech Stack: ASP.NET MVC, Angular.js, SQL Server, Entity Framework, JavaScript, Bootstrap

.NET Developer - Permanent - Remote

January 2013 - June 2015

**BuCons, Outsourcing to HSO Business School** 

Developed, documented and delivered a lot of small applications like webshops, windows services, etc. The main application was a Desktop Win Forms application used for the administration of the scores and profiles of the students. Worked with the team of HSO from Switzerland remotely until the delivery. Trained a junior. Waterfall methodology.

Tech Stack: AWS, WinForms, DotNet Bar, WPF, XBAP ASP.NET MVC/WebForms, DotNetNuke, SQL Server, Entity Framework

## **EDUCATION**

**Bachelor's of Informatics** 

**September 2010 – July 2014** 

University of Plovdiv, Business IT

.NET (A), Java (A), Design Patterns (A), C++ (A), Banking (A), Finance (A), Accounting (A), Excel (A)

#### SKILLS

Technologies – AWS, Azure, ASP.NET MVC/WebForms/Web API, ASP.NET Core, WinForms, WPF, Angular, Vue.js, Umbraco, Selenium, SQL Server, WinServices, EntityFramework Core, xUnit Test, Docker, Git, jQuery, Bootstrap

Languages - English, Bulgarian, C#, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SQL, SpecFlow, Docker, TypeScript

## **HOBBIES & INTERESTS**

Outside of work, I love visiting the gym and going hiking sometimes. I am going to different activities and events to open my creativity. In my free time, I am reading books and watching movies.

## REFERENCES

SHAULA ZANCHI, HEAD OF IT SERVICES, FOSTER + PARTNERS
RIVERSIDE, 22 HESTER RD, LONDON, SW11 4AN / 07789716738 / SZANCHI@FOSTERANDPARTNERS.COM

IVAILO IVANOV, CTO, BGO SOFTWARE

BUL. "TSAR BORIS III" 159, SOFIA / +359884678299 / IVAILO.IVANOV@BGOSOFTWARE.COM

ANDERS PERSON, CEO, COMSTREAM

PROF. ALEXANDER TANEV 11 FL. 4, SOFIA / +359879828500 / AP@COMSTREAM.SE